BLANCHE
Irina ? No.. She left with Walter Grey yesterday in the morning. You didn't know ?

DOLORES
Yes I know but apparently she's back. I saw her enter the building yesterday, around 10 AM.

BLANCHE
I don't get it. If anything happened and she had to cancel she would have come to me..

DOLORES
Maybe she was embarrassed and wanted some alone time ?

BLANCHE
I.. I don't know what to say or think about this right now but..

BLANCHE
Thanks for telling me. It's getting late I really should grab the whip and go meet my clients in the hall.

DOLORES
Toughen up Bee. You've got this. Guess I'll do my hair myself.