BLANCHE
Dolores ? Are you done ?

DOLORES
Yes. I'm getting ready for my next booking now.

BLANCHE
Mireille asked me to bring you these shoes.

BLANCHE
Apparently it's very important that you wear them with your next guy..

DOLORES
I get it. I will wear them. Just put them on the floor. If that's it, you can go, thanks.

DOLORES
I wonder if Irina could do my hair if she's around... She's good at this.