BLANCHE
Here's your meds.. You should take those pills.

NIKKI
I..AM NOT CRAZY. I.. can feel that they’re in danger.

BLANCHE
Would me checking on them calm you down a little ?

BLANCHE
I’m sure I can prove you that they’re doing fine.

BLANCHE
I’ll ask Barney, he always knows what became of everyone.

BLANCHE
Or I could ask Ray ? He’s a policeman after all.. Knows how to investigate.

NIKKI
I can hear them !! NO NOT OUTSIDE TOO ! I have to go !