BLANCHE
Karma ! I was looking for you ! Do you have a minute ?

MAGGIE
Well, i'm in good hands right now.. Can't you see ?

MAGGIE
Or do you want to take them away from me like some other bitch I know.

BLANCHE
Wh..What ?

BLANCHE
No ! I'm here to thank you. Because of you Irina isn't gonna get fired if she comes back quickly.

MAGGIE
Hahah that's the funniest thing i've heard all day. Now leave me alone.