BLANCHE
Dotty ! Listen to me : Tom's in the dormitories right now. You can calm down..

DOTTY
I.. I messed up again.. I'm the shittiest mom ever..

BLANCHE
No you're..

DOTTY
Please don't try to comfort me, you're that bitch's friend..

BLANCHE
I have no idea what you're talking about but i'll go ask Barney for a "special remedy".

BLANCHE
You can pick it up later when you'll feel better.

DOTTY
Thank.. Thank's Bee.