BLANCHE
You don't understand ! She told me that she would come back today.

RAY
<clumsy>Well.. uhm..</clumsy> She was here yesterday.. In this <yeah>very</yeah> room. She <clumsy>was..</clumsy> with another girl.

RAY
The girl was really <sad>wasted</sad> and they didn't really seem to get along...

BLANCHE
Why wouldn't you tell me this in the first place ? You're acting strange <b><b>Ray</b></b>..

RAY
For real little girl, quit being such a <sad>nosy ass</sad> all the time..

BLANCHE
Perhaps I'm not being nosy enough.

RAY
Stay out of this Bee, I'm sure <b><b>Irina</b></b>'s fine wherever she is right now.